#### Your Basket

Your basket is empty.

* Your Account

* Change Currency

#### Your Basket

Your basket is empty.

Added to Basket

b373b80a0b877e2534686542bfefa859

$ USD

[Login](https://www.sojourner.biz/login.html) / [Register](https://www.sojourner.biz/register.html)

Please enter a search keyword

Please enter a search keyword

* Shop by Category

##### Shop by Category

    * Clasps
    * Jewelry
    * Beads
        * Stone A-L
        * Stone M-Z

Back

* JavaScript is required by this website. Please enable this in your browser settings.

Privacy Policy
--------------

**Our Commitment To Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to Sojourner. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and how your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available from the footer of every page.

**The Information We Collect**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Sojourner website. On some pages, you can order products or request information. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:  
Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information  
(etc.)

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s name and address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:  
Name  
Address  
Phone Number  
(etc.)

**The Way We Use Information**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to keep you informed about the status of pending orders. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. We may also use your email address to send you information about Sojourner if you [subscribe to our mailing list](https://www.sojourner.biz/list/?p=subscribe).

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above, except as required by law.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website.

We use cookies to record session information, such as items that you add to your shopping cart. We also use cookies to record your preferences, such as whether you prefer a grid or list view. You can use the buttons at the top of this page to allow or block cookies other than the main session cookie and the cookie preference cookie. You may also delete any www.sojourner.biz cookies if you prefer after you complete your order.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. All customer information in the online store is encrypted, and credit card numbers are automatically purged from the database when the transaction is completed. (That’s why we must ask for your credit card information again to process a refund.)

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 16 years old, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 16.

**How To Contact Us**  
You may ask to review, correct, update, or delete the personal information that you have previously provided to us by emailing us at privacy@sojourner.biz. If you have registered for an account on our website you may generally update your user settings and profile by logging into that account. Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at privacy@sojourner.biz.

To contact our data protection officer, email security@sojourner.biz.

**Policy Updates**  
Sojourner may revise this policy as needed by updating this posting.

### Featured Product

#### [12 mm by 8 mm top-drilled vintage frosted blue-green glass leaves](https://www.sojourner.biz/beads/glass/12-mm-by-8-mm-top-drilled-vintage-frosted-blue-green-glass-leaves.html "12 mm by 8 mm top-drilled vintage frosted blue-green glass leaves")

$6.00

### Best Sellers

1. [Vintage Italian chevron beads](https://www.sojourner.biz/beads/glass/vintage-italian-chevron-beads.html "Vintage Italian chevron beads")  
    $6.00
2. [Snowstorm clasp](https://www.sojourner.biz/clasps/glass/snowstorm-clasp.html "Snowstorm clasp")  
    $16.00
3. [Square pearl clasp](https://www.sojourner.biz/clasps/pearl/square-pearl-clasp.html "Square pearl clasp")  
    $16.00
4. [Neon blue Swarovski polka dot clasp](https://www.sojourner.biz/clasps/swarovski/neon-blue-swarovski-polka-dot-clasp.html "Neon blue Swarovski polka dot clasp")  
    $15.00
5. [White pearl toggle clasp](https://www.sojourner.biz/clasps/toggles/white-pearl-toggle-clasp.html "White pearl toggle clasp")  
    $28.00
6. [Red bar clasp](https://www.sojourner.biz/clasps/glass/red-bar-clasp.html "Red bar clasp")  
    $23.00
7. [Mother-of-pearl box clasp](https://www.sojourner.biz/clasps/pearl/mother-of-pearl-box-clasp.html "Mother-of-pearl box clasp")  
    $17.00
8. [Citrine clasp](https://www.sojourner.biz/clasps/faux-stone/citrine-clasp.html "Citrine clasp")  
    $26.00
9. [Sterling silver tiny lily clasp](https://www.sojourner.biz/clasps/sterling-only/sterling-silver-tiny-lily-clasp.html "Sterling silver tiny lily clasp")  
    $10.00
10. [Turquoise bar toggle clasp](https://www.sojourner.biz/clasps/toggles/turquoise-bar-toggle-clasp.html "Turquoise bar toggle clasp")  
    $13.50

### Information

Site copyright 2024 Sojourner. All rights reserved.

### Follow Us

Site copyright 2024 Sojourner. All rights reserved.
